the the seminar is recorded as usual and
will be made available on our youtube channel
um if you continue participating in the
seminar after recording it means that you agree
for the recording to be publicly disseminated i
would recommend you mute your microphone and turn
off your camera if you don't want to be seen or
heard um so i want to thank the magnets team greg
anik richard dan that started this and this is
going well um i'm really happy of this series of
seminar i hope you're enjoying them as well and
so we'll have about 20-30 minutes presentation
um if you it's an informal uh place so if you
need to go don't worry about it seminar recorded
there is going to be time for 10-15
minutes questions and discussion
and then there is gonna be a time for catch up
which is not recorded and i hope you can stay um
so for today i'm really happy that we have uber
kirke from to begin in germany uh talking about
assembly of proto-australia during the formation
of the nuna super continent in the palo pali
thanks uber the floor is
yours thank you um scream too
all right can you see this my screen yeah
okay okay so okay thank you very much for
the opportunity yeah to give this talk that's
that's very nice um yeah to keep in touch with
the community in these times and um so i'm going
to talk about yeah the um stuff i've been doing
over the past years really um starting the time
when i was in australia together with with lee
in in curtin in perth and so i was working mainly
on on the nuna super continent so um yeah i will
i will start with the introduction about super
continents and and the like the precambrian um
view we have right now and on the evolution of
the yeah really the pilot geography in on on earth
in the last let's say two billion years or and
beyond like um and in this time the the in the
paleogeography really the um the concept
of supercontinents is really one of the
the dominating one in in this time and um yeah so
this is a small picture about from a restaurant i
found in in tubing in so the noonan the name
is really a bit misleading because it's it's
coming from from paul offman's view of florentia
so i think like continents bordering the northern
ocean so but but still it it was kept being there
so so now it's called nuna or colombia which which
is really only a name so but i started with nuna
so i i kind of stick with it so to begin with just
um i had this in in another presentation but um um
like starting working on it i i um the interesting
thing about about nuna is really the to me the
how how the earth really transitioned towards
an earth where we kind of think we understand most
of the things and one of the the key mechanism
like mechanisms on earth is really plate tectonics
and especially when it's related as we see today
with with mantle dynamics and and the long-term
antler evolution and and as we know now that that
only with plate tectonics um the the climate on
on a long time scale um cam um can stay stable so
um this is like with the with weathering in in
subduction zones and weathering of like basaltic
large english provinces and stuff like that is
only with that the the um the climate on earth can
be stable over a long period of time and at least
as i understand it we needed this time for for
complex life to evolve i mean we're not sure how
this how this took place but we know that there
was a long time when when like single cell stuff
was was already existing until the the like the
explosion of life in the end of the precambrian
and then i mean also an interesting thing which
is not that um i think understood that well is
that the biodiversity is really um um or can be
connected to the um like if the if all continents
were together or separated so we need kind of
a mosaic of plates for the biodiversity
to to expand or at least it's related so
all these things um lead to the to the assumption
that we really need plate tectonics um on our
for the for earth to become a habitable planet
and that makes it interesting um to look at other
planets and say okay if it is it even possible on
other planets um to to to for life to to evolve or
like what do we need for for other planets but
there's i mean this all a bit like just to to
make it interesting is not so much what i i
will talk about but um so there was this um
kind of battle i don't i don't know who of you
heard this about uh um with with tara scarier and
bob stern on one hand like the the evolutionary
people and then the uniformitarian people
and i thought this was very interesting because
this is a big problem in especially in the palu
geographic evolution and to start um like tyra's
gary especially and also bobster they say um
the like the transition from a like a venus-like
squishy lit tectonics planet towards a modern
style plate tectonics earth um it took a long
time when when transitional what they call
transitional tectonics took place and is really
not not sure how long did this take took and
they claimed that even like before one billion
years ago or maybe even later only then would
it be possible to to um like to have this this
plate tectonics modern style plate tectonics
earth what we have today like when we have a lot
of um like the mosaic of plates like connected
to the to to like mental convection and to to
these large low shear wave velocity provinces
and this supercontinent cycle as we understand it
also this um and they claim with with especially
tara's with with some modeling that this
cannot be at two billion years ago this was
not possible because the mantle was just hotter
and all the the subducting plates was just um
just um dripping off but on the other hand like
when we we the the approach we make with with
the super continent cycle is really this picture
which um like i've seen a lot of times and then
i mean you you see pangaea obviously i mean a lot
of people working on that and then there's rodinia
which is like more or less um yeah a lot of people
like think it's fine like they know how it looks
like there's still debates like in all these these
old times you always have debates but then this if
you draw this picture like there is another super
continent we're fairly sure about that and but if
if you start this you say okay there was super
continent cycles throughout earth history maybe
as only three billion years ago and what these
other like the evolutionary people say that this
just cannot work in the same way as as it works
today so um like the onset of plate tectonics this
is a like a bit of a misleading term because plate
tectonics is like different people um would define
it very differently but yeah this just to show
that there's there's a a a time span where where
different people would say very different things
about the about the onset of of plate tectonics
so just a a slide on the super continent
segment to me this is really the most um yeah
maybe significant paper of lee and
together with gigi chong where they um um
like they make kind of the the concept of the
super continent cycle and it's the present day the
like as we see today with with the two lls
vps and then there were papers about the
future super continent i mean there's
also different suggestions there is um
like panchiya that the old superconduct we all
know about and i mean there's always the the
problem that there also was gonda so what
is actually a supercontinent there's also
like how many of the continents actually have to
be together to define a supercontinent and and
which is the real supercontinent and then there's
rodinia and then there is um like the suggestion
of these ancient super blooms or ancient llcps
and then lee draw this this picture of of the the
like intensity of plume events where he saw some
cyclicity and there definitely is some cyclicity
but i mean if it if it's that easy or not that's
this very debated i think but yeah then he he made
this like um some of the the reconstructions
of rodinia where they form somewhere
and then they they create the super plume beneath
them and then true polar wonder will put them on
the on the pilot equator which is rotationally
more stable and i mean then the the the key
thing of this paper is really that they like she
she made this modeling like where blue is down
welling i think and then yellow is upwelling and
they started with a like a random distribution
and then they showed that this will always like
the the downwellings will will cluster and and
then lead to the supercond information on top
of of this and then this super continent with
with um yeah with the the subduction
ring around them will create the like
old slab material and this will create and
then a super plume and this would in the end
destroy the super continent and then it will
this girdle will move and this will the next
super content will form and this is kind of the
yeah the this the concept of how supercontinents
or how this cycling is is working and more
recently um ross and and chong wang wrote this
geology paper where they they argued um yeah based
on some geochemistry arguments that there was
always this pairing of mega continents with super
content this is kind of the attempt to to solve
this gondwana panchayat thing and i mean what you
yeah yeah this is all very very conceptual this is
um to me this is not really like um the the key
thing i mean what is interesting to note is that
a lot of times the the assembly of the one
super continent is really overlapping with the
with the destruction of the old one so the and
this is all related to how you actually define
the super continent cycle and how you define a
super continent and and so there's a lot of to
me still a lot of problems and a lot of this
is related to that people want to make this
a very um cyclic um evolution like this all has
to be the same so there has to um this this the
tenure of one super continent has to stay the same
or less and yeah i mean since there is a lot of um
uncertainty this is all possible so yeah but
in the end this is the like the status we have
right now and i mean as you have seen before we
that the limits were pushed further back and and
um other super contests were also proposed and um
i'm concerning this issue on a on a like a key and
super continent um one of the stu the phd students
at curtin at the time i was there was studying
uh dyke dykes in in like um in the west
australian creighton so so close to perth
and this is a great area he made his phd there
and he was doing palumek on all these dykes and um
um in the past it was believed that there was just
one or two dyke swarms but he actually showed with
with um geochronology which was another phd
that there's many um like different um dyke
swarms of very different age between 2.6 and and
like um i don't know the youngest are like 700.
so um these red ones are the uh the the ikea dikes
and he has had very nice results like close to
this is um susceptibility with temperature close
to to pure magnetite um curry temperatures and a
nice nice directions and he compared this with
so does that even do a polarity the results the
side mean directions and he compared this with
other other results from from this area and
there was no um like um i mean we couldn't
perform an actual back contact test but
the main argument was to a polarity to some extent
and then that they don't the mean don't coincide
with with other um other results from this
area and the mean temperature component even
might be related to the mother like swarm
like a bit younger 2.4 and this is a 2.6
so this um um yeah we argue that this is an
argument that this is actual primary directions
and um this is a compilation of zimbabwe
and gilgans of west australian craton and
he had two possibilities where i mean that the
orientation is still not not decided but the the
the main result to me is these are his two
options so the super continent solution
where we tried really hard to put together all
creators at the time which was um proposed before
to form a super continent and this is possible
but only if there's two separate super continents
at 2.6 and 2.4 which a lot of motion in between
relative motion but the the much more likely um
option to me is that actually two clusters of
of gritons were were present at this time where
as i said this was the time where keno
land of the ikea super content was proposed
and to me this is good evidence so not much
actual blade motion is necessary this could
even be true polar wonder because both clusters
moving the same way but this to me shows that
that the it's much more likely that these
classes of creators were present in the ikea and
like super continents really only
started in the in the proterozoic
so and um now to the to the the proteosox
the super condi and nuna if there was no
ikean super continent then noona might
really be the first one and so this is um
luna is a very interesting one because um it um
it this is um the trial circon um just counts and
on one hand it has a huge um significant
peak there so a lot of stuff was formed
at this time and not only the super continent
form but but closed like two billion years ago
most of the major cratons formed like laurentia
baltica australia they all formed at this time and
then they all came together so it seems that this
really represents a special time in earth history
and then what uh mccolly did both one is that
he he did some some size a very detailed seismic
profile in north china and and he argued that
this um the results look very similar to what
he's seen in the himalaya and then he compared
this with other other results and he claimed
at the end that this um was the first time
that actually large-scale tectonic systems
were in place by during at 1.8 during
the formation of the lunar supercontinent
and he claimed this was really the onset of
plate tectonics and what we then did is we we
studied 1.3 billion year old darum
darim silt from north australia and um
so this is our updated configuration of nuna dis
laurentia um siberian baltic this is what what
people say that the core of nuna david evans
called it that and um um richard ernst made
some some um correlations with dykes and and
claimed that this was really a long history of
um but but this is not not that big and we added
australia and north china with some yeah with
paleomag data and also the correlation of this
of these seals and dikes and and this is our
then proposal how nuna actually looked like and
this is really a proper size sized super continent
so this is at that 1.3 this when this was and
this is how we so we made um also not only
paleo mac and and and actually the the that
the seals were or that the configuration of
the dikes but also the um like the toc record of
the shama ling formation the vicari formation here
that they showed the same excursion that like yeah
more or less similar times and what i then did is
i made a compilation of all poles if if nuna
was was really like this between 1.7 and 1.3
and i mean there's some wiggling but but generally
a a combined apparent polar wonder path is really
possible at least for for nuna and it shows
that it just rotated very slightly at the
equator at that time all right then um to move to
the the assembly of nunad um we studied at 1.1.79
or 1.8 um ga um um a hard dollar right
in australia and there we proposed that
um like the one of the key connections in the nuna
super con is between la rancho and australia from
from like apart from this core of nuna thing
and this apart from a small reorganization
between 1.73 and 1.65 it this was um
all like already connected at 1.8 so
to me the the like even though people argue that
that the nuna only formed a 1.6 but not much
happened between 1.8 and 1.6 and this is kind
of similar to what happened in um in rodinia
and maybe also in pancreas with the like this
mega shear for example this this um evolutions
like this like reorganization of super continents
once it they've formed might not be so so unusual
and um so then the um the two new things which are
not published yet but which i'm i'm working on now
is um to further um like now characterize how how
nuna actually assembled so before or around 1.8
so what what happened and if because if we can um
if we can further describe this disassembly then
we might be able to com actually compare the the
assembly of nuna with with other super continents
because as i said before the it might really be
the the first of its of its kind and and might um
represent a big transition in in the geographic
evolution of the earth so i went to two places
one one is is at the kimberley craton in north
australia yeah in the in the western part of
north australia and then in the the palm tree
creek volcanics which they were supposed to be
close in age i mean if if like i'm also not only
working the precambrian and 30 million years is a
long time but um in the precambrian or especially
in the paleo producer we have to do like the best
we can and this where the two places with the most
promising rocks like like a ring in the toby ring
intrusion mafic um ring intrusion in the kimberley
craton and then and then like a bimodal volcanics
in the um yeah close to darwin and and yeah they
are they are not the same age but as i said yeah
this this what the the two of the most promising
targets to compare the pilot geography just before
the the assembly of luna and yeah these again
the age ranges so this is the tobii intrusion
is the plum tree and to to make a better kind
of comparison we also measure the vgp of another
intrusion like a wild dog creek intrusion which is
close to the tobe intrusion and these are the two
orochinis which which uh supposed to to
um represent the the assembly of the north
australian crater so this is really related to the
assembly of of australia that's what we know and
so my my goal was to to see how this fits in the
global the global framework of assembly of nuna
and is the ring intrusion very beautiful like
the green stuff here is the tobii intrusion
and this is our sampling sites
this is this the location here
and this is the result very nice again i mean
this is all the stuff i i all the dyke seals
mafix stuff i worked on and from the from
australia they look the same like these kt curves
and and af alternating feeling and thermal dmac
look pretty similar and these are the side mean
directions and the overall mean direction very
shallow um and the argument to say it's it might
really be a primary one is there was another
another study by austin and paterson in 2020
they studied a also ring intrusion a bit north
of of our intrusion and they found this direction
which is very close to the direction we found in
the durham durham sea from 1.3 billion years old
and they claim is a remagnitization based on
some other arguments some ams arguments and um
yeah because this is not not at all what we're
seeing in our results that's made us believe that
that this actually um should be a a primary poll
um um yeah we tried to do some back contact test
but i mean this is really like heavily weathered
you don't you don't see a lot of outcrops
and i mean no contacts at all in this area so
we have some over prints some present day and
some some very steep ones which are also reported
in other areas but yeah so so this is all the all
the arguments we have and then the so the plum
tree creek volcanics is a bit of a tricky target
because they have been studied a lot of times in
the past by by um uh evans heart and uh yeah um
since it's like the 70s or something and then
they have been restarted by it no man giddings but
um all this is not properly presented so so we we
went there again to to restudy them and see if we
get the same results and now i'm in
the in the process of of i'm getting
together with these other people which are
um not all retired but are all um yeah not
actively working on this anymore but they all
have still results from the plum tree mechanics
and i i want to put everything together but yeah
i will show you my results which so this is the
this is the the place where they are like one
point at their age changed a bit not that much
and then there is um the above the edits river
group there is a techno metamorphic event at 1.78
and then not much is happening after that so the
the the north australian craton is i mean this is
we have this um um we have evidence for this
from from other places that not really not
much happened in the in this area after this time
this is the results of the side effects again um
and um the problem is that the the batting is is
really not much there is a like a sink line but um
the bedding attitudes are really not not that it's
not foldy very much so we have this picture where
it looks it looks fairly similar and we get a
sin falling maximum clustering but not not a
lot of variation so my goal really is to compare
this with the with other data which the raw data
was not presented in this in these old studies
so um they they promised me to dig out the the
raw data and then i want to redo this but a a soon
folding event might only be possible at this 1.78
event and and we don't see a um like this is
the result we don't see that they agree with the
with the dollar right which is the more or less
the same age so this is the my poll from the hot
dollar right this is the old plum tree pole and
the new one they they they agree fairly well with
each other so um yeah this for now we um i i will
take it as a yeah as a poll with that more more
stuff needs to be done to really verify that this
is the primary poll but yeah around 1.8 is this
um this is the result for now and these are the
the two results from the tobii intrusion and um
so and this is a comparison with all the data from
this area and the the first and most interesting
result is that they they all cluster in this
area like this is really data between 1.8 ga
and um like 1.65 when when it starts to to
move away the the the the polio pose and
then there is some slide motion and whatever this
wiggling is but um um my my argument would be
that that if the toby and white dog if they they
agree fairly well with each other if they they are
more or less the same age as this palm tree pole
then like as a really small rotation between the
the kimberley and and the north australian
craton so this is the kimberly's these two
and the plum trees this one here and this
would would be sufficient to to assemble that
like brought to australia as they they put it
so um make this a bit more um with a bit more
bigger maps and more like pilot geographic
information like this is from before
if we if we use this this is a um yeah like the
h is is really vaguely defined and i used like a
we have a reconstruction 1.88 which everything is
a bit more loosely defined but and then we have a
like this is our our reconstruction at 1.8
and if we i mean really not much is it's
is is necessary and if this um is um is is
related to just the just in um putting the
all the gratins closer together and this might be
then the reason why the kimberley and australia
made this rotation and this um this um movement
um together to form nuna this might have been
the reason for for this rotation to take place and
um to further like investigate if oops if the um
if this can be possible like north china here this
was um yeah where bovan was working and he this is
the the um trans china um zone here and um so if
this is if reasonable to put the kimberly craton
close to the north china crest gretna at this time
we i was looking at at the trial circum data from
there's a big compilation by hollis in in 2014
and they had this this like new ikea and peak had
around 2.5 ga and they have fairly positive epson
afghan values and they were relating this either
to another area in north australia or to india
but what i would say is that this fits very well
to the eastern block of north china with with
very similar ages so this is now granites and
all sorts of primary data and all the similar
apps on half new values so this the trial circon
populations here might really come from the from
the eastern part of the north china gratin so this
like configuration of luna prior to assembly
might really make sense so they all come from
from this area this oh there's a lot of rocks of
this age there india of course is might also be
there but then i mean we need more data india has
like more data is coming but we really have not
enough information to really verify the
results already there so um like this is all
in in progress this this refining this um the the
pilot geography but what what to me is interesting
and and what i think is we should like geographers
in this in this age we should not try to to
identify the super continents which i mean this
we have done a lot of a long time but um to me the
nuna assembly really looks a bit different to what
what we would expect and apparently at even before
1.8 this all these these the the creators forming
they were all already close to the paleo equator
and then just just slide um like yeah um moving
together let them to the formation of nuna then
some some stuff was going on but this was really a
long period of time and um reading the um this gsa
article by bob stern this i really wonder if
this um this more reflects the the transition
towards the super continent cycle which just
starts with rodinia and not before and and this
the long existence of nuna was really i mean
i mean maybe not i mean it depends on what you
what you think about a single lit tectonics but
this this this slow rotation this slow assembly
of nuna might be it might be more um yeah i mean
not true but it might be more to more reasonable
to say that this is is related to like a single
tectonic um evolution rather than a like a proper
um modern style plate tectonics evolution
all right thank you that was a bit long but
that was great thank you very much hugo for your
presentation let's give a big round of applause
maybe you can unshare your screen i think
we can see your email sorry it's okay
yeah thanks a lot very
interesting thank you very much
uh it's now time for questions if there is any
um
you can oh okay there is one question from
nicole uh does the upwelly and down well in
location driven by rotation access right slide
four uh wait um i don't think i i understood the
question sorry i'll try to reach richard
do you think you understand the question
oh um oh nicole thanks yes please express
yourself um so slide four um i think
if it was some modeling of like um yeah yes should
i share it again yeah that would be nice but um
was that like the it kept getting like the
same i think you said that they kept getting
somewhat like the same results but like is the
upwelling like location in dell dan welling the
like green or the blue and red um uh oh wait
wait wait wait i think okay this one here yeah
yeah yeah and i was just curious like is it like
is there like um like is the the rotation axis and
then the rate have to like does that play a role
do you think that would play a role in like where
the um welding would be yeah yeah no no definitely
i mean as far as i understand this this the
formation where it takes place is rather like
wherever if they they form somewhere and then
true polar wonder would bring it to
the equator because this i mean this
is an excess in mass where you have a lot of this
this um subduction a lot of plates so the rotation
stability we put it to the equator that's how
i understand the model and i'm not sure how um
i never i never saw a talk by sushi about this
so i as far as i i understand the papers this
this is a self-organizing process of the the the
like the individual down wellings they they've
come together and then they form this this super
down welling and then it moves to the equator
and then it it goes from there there is some some
problem in connecting the the four steps i think
like this was not out automatically happening
as far as i understand it but yeah there's
at the um concerning where where it
happens i i don't really know if if they
if they have any any specific results on that or
if this is just one result or if the if this may
look different in different runs i i don't
know when you say um it goes to the equator
you mean like the super consonant tends to the
equator yeah so so true polar wonder so it's
um like the whole um the whole continent mantle
crust mantle thing moves relative to the spin axis
this is the the argument because there's yeah
there's if you have this i mean the it makes sense
that this this llc piece and the super continent
uh at the equator and a very interesting thing is
that the only time when this happened apparently
is rodinia and i don't know if this is if this is
so um if everyone believes this is this is true
but it's interesting that nuna formed at the
equator and and pangea also formed kind of at the
equator so i mean at some point i i mean i would
even say the you could even say that they were
there the whole time like what um other people
more work in the final story i think they argue
from a nuna perspective this can as well be true
like that you know that there's like these mantles
lower mantle structures are stable over the whole
period of time and the super content forming
get destroyed i'm like independent of that but
but yeah i mean there's a lot of there's a lot of
unknowns definitely in this in this in this story
thank you thank you for your question and thanks
for the answer uber uh someone else's questions
um if i can i'll jump in with a question
um the interest i'm really fascinating you
talked a little bit about how nuna it sort
of stalled or there was a reconfiguration
and then you kind of mentioned you've
seen that in other super continents is it
did does it seem to have like the same style
of stalling do you have any idea what's kind
of happening or is it just sort of something
that happened in nuna that sort of stood out
yeah i mean um like nuna we really have not a lot
of data and and what we saw is that we like you
could you could do this like the fitting the poles
is better matched by a different configuration and
one way to get there is is a is a strike slip
reorientation and they been then proposed this
for rodinia to like this story about the missing
link and the mega she is also like that and i mean
working on nuna like there's so many
uncertainties and we don't really know
a lot so i wouldn't i wouldn't say
that okay this has to be the same but
but i always thought okay i mean you put that
you you smash together a bunch of continents
and if the the configuration is not perfect then
you would have like you would try to make it round
let's say because this is like you have a lot of
subduction everywhere and if it's if it's pushing
more on one side then you would you would get it
um a better line maybe i don't know but i'm i just
like this is just i i thought it interesting
when i saw this paper from being when that
this happened also in rodinia and i think yeah
the style is really looks similar because it's
yeah strike slip motion between big parts of
of the of the super continent and yeah maybe
thank you that's it's it's
it's interesting i'm trying to
process you know like you said there's so little
data you have to yeah yeah work hard to fill it
all in yeah i mean there's still a lot of a lot
of uncertainties in in this i i always think it's
it's very interesting how how how the the bows
are like how this configuration of nuna can be
can be so close together and this is and because
i would say this it is it seems to be the first
one then the assembly story of nuna might really
be an interesting part where we we need more data
obviously and it's like working getting new
poles in the in the pre-camera this is it's a
it's a bit of a frustrating story because you
you have to you have to work hard and then you
get one small um additional piece and then you you
put a continent a bit further away like the plum
tree old pole this was a good poll and now we went
there again and we did it again and we put and at
the end it will it will end up at the same at the
same position and then we're still not not sure
if this like the whole remagnetization thing this
is a big problem and then we don't and especially
if you have ports close together you don't really
know and getting a big contact test is sometimes
so difficult in this in this area so yeah i
mean we have to yeah keep working i guess and
thanks we understand very well the frustration
of having a lot of work and a very good data
out of that maybe you can unshare your screen so
somebody else has a question that wants to share
i had a uh all right thanks ahmed um the
you you base your is this possibly
re-magnetized on on the full test and um
since i think you used my fold test uh
i i'm wondering what happens if you add
i mean it's just barely not a hundred right so i
was wondering what happens if you add uncertainty
in the in the in the orientations uh-huh well
there is that option there used to be when i
first published it that you could you know like
have an uncertainty in the in the polls to the
planes and then you add that uncertainty
in that'll widen your your error bars yeah
you know strikes and dips exactly and
so um you could you could get a 100
that's great i i was wondering about this
a lot of times and i always assume that you
i mean yeah i always like i calculated the mean
betting because like a lot of in these cases
i took 10 10 betting measurements and they are
like sometimes very different and then i i take
okay this is also related to the measurement and
maybe this is the mean and then i apply the mean
but yeah and the way that you did it you assume
that you know that perfectly but then if you
if you sub if you did a monte carlo sampling of
the actual distribution of betting planes too
and if it's not in this current version of the um
full test it could be added easily i i think it is
in there okay i have to look for it that's that's
a great thing yeah and then you just kind of say
it could be a hundred yes yeah i mean to me i was
happy that it's not zero so it's is he's not like
after folding so yeah but probably not pre-folding
and it's um i i'm i'm sure that if you add in the
uncertainty in the bet yeah that you'll widen that
and you'll include 100 okay that's great thanks
i will try that if the code needs some work just
let me know yes yes no this is a great code this
thank god it's there and this like python these
scripts i use like linux and then you can script
all this and he's very nice like there's so
many guys they're even better they're wonderful
i don't know if they work on on linux
okay well thanks thanks thanks lisa thanks uma
i think unless there is some burning
question i think we can uh we can wrap
up we want to thank again uber with another
big round of applause thank you very much